<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>路Warren Fernandes路</title>
    <link>https://wfernandes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 路Warren Fernandes路</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://wfernandes.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Creating a New Theme</title>
      <link>https://wfernandes.github.io/post/creating-a-new-theme/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wfernandes.github.io/post/creating-a-new-theme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initial Commit</title>
      <link>https://wfernandes.github.io/post/init_commit/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 18:33:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wfernandes.github.io/post/init_commit/</guid>
      <description>Hello World.
First let me start off by saying how exciting this is. Yeah yeah..every one these days has a blog so you might ask what&amp;rsquo;s so special about this one. The answer is&amp;hellip;Nothing.
I&amp;rsquo;m technically doing this for my own personal satisfaction.
I have a few motives that are driving me to regularly contribute to this blog.
Firstly, I have a goal to contribute to more open source software. I&amp;rsquo;m primarily a Golang developer now, but I have done some Java and Javascript in the past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://wfernandes.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://wfernandes.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>whoami I am a husband to a loving wife.
I am the master overlord to my pitty-puppy.
I am a software engineer who yearns to contribute to a greater goal.
I am a citizen to a world that desperately needs help.
whyami I see myself as an engineer who wishes to contribute to projects that better this world.
Sounds corny&amp;hellip;yeah I agree, but don&amp;rsquo;t think I could have put it any any other way.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>